Contact

aleksandar.borisovski@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/borisovski (LinkedIn)

borisovski.my.canva.site/aboutme (Blog)

Top Skills

Business Cards
Business Card Design
business card

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Serbian (Professional Working)
Czech (Elementary)
Croatian (Professional Working)
Macedonian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Academy for Digital marketing + WordPress

Aleksandar Borisovski

Co-Founder at MN-Connect, Graphic Designer & Digital Marketer Bitola, Pelagonia, North Macedonia

Summary

Greetings, I am Aleksandar Borisovski, a 24-year-old Macedonian resident.

I'm a creative and open-minded individual.

Co-Founder at MN-Connect, Graphic Designer & Digital Marketer.

In addition, I have strong understanding of cryptocurrency and have skills designing websites and video editing.

About me: https://borisovski.my.canva.site/aboutme

Experience

MN Connect Co-Founder May 2024 - Present (2 months)

Crypto Beast Trading
Crypto Trader
June 2021 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Binance, OKX, PancakeSwap, ByBit, MetaMask, Mexc, Phantom, and Toonkeeper.

Superior familiarity with the platforms. knowledge of trading on Cross Margin, or Futures.

Abundant expertise in cryptocurrency transfers and wallet creation.

Graphic Days 4 years 5 months

Graphic Cover February 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

North Macedonia

Stickers

February 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

North Macedonia

Graphic Design's

February 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

North Macedonia

With more than three years of experience, I specialize in crafting captivating graphics, poster, brochure, stickers & logo that resonate with audiences..

I excel in understanding each brand's unique identity and translating it into visually compelling designs.

Let's collaborate to elevate your brand's visual presence.

Logo Design's

February 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

North Macedonia

Business Cards

February 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Pop Up Bar Prague

Cocktail Bartender

April 2023 - October 2023 (7 months)

Prague, Czechia

Cocktail - Bartender in Czech Republic, Prague

Jagoda Meze-Bar

Bartender

October 2022 - April 2023 (7 months)

Bitola, Pelagonia, North Macedonia

Buffet Bribirska Obala

Buffet Waiter

May 2022 - October 2022 (6 months)

Novi Vinodolski, Primorje-Gorski, Croatia

Buffet Waiter

Timely order receipt

Offer recommendations and daily deals to consumers

Friendly, cheerful and polite attitude

A strong passion for ensuring customer satisfaction

Barista's Coffee Shop
Bar Waiter
October 2021 - April 2022 (7 months)

Dio Modern Mediterranean Graphic Designer November 2021 - January 2022 (3 months) Tampa, Florida, United States

hustler4freedom Instagram Business February 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 9 months) North Macedonia

My Instagram business started in February 2020 i had several successfull instagram accounts.

It was an amazing experience! During that period, I mentored over 20 clients throughout that time.

9ForLife 5 months

Entrepreneur April 2021 - August 2021 (5 months) Republic of Macedonia

Networker, Speaker

Network Marketing April 2021 - August 2021 (5 months) Republic of Macedonia

Networker, Speaker

Kromberg & Schubert Operator October 2020 - April 2021 (7 months) Bitola, Pelagonia, North Macedonia

Operator in production for Audi

PIZZERIA NAVA, Novi Vinodolski

Buffet Waiter

May 2019 - September 2019 (5 months)

Novi Vinodolski, Primorje-Gorski, Croatia

Buffet Waiter

Timely order receipt

Offer recommendations and daily deals to consumers

Friendly, cheerful and polite attitude

A strong passion for ensuring customer satisfaction

Ciflik Winery

Buffet Waiter

February 2019 - April 2019 (3 months)

CERMAT

Assistant Distrubuter

May 2018 - March 2019 (11 months)

Truck Assistant Distrubuter

Ice Factory

Producing and Delivering Ice

June 2015 - September 2016 (1 year 4 months)

Producing and delivering ice

Education

OSMU "Dr. Jovan Kalauzi" Bitola

· (September 2014 - June 2018)